FEEL THE POWER OF YOUR VOICE!

Connecting issues? Please download the latest Voicemod version [Download Now!](https://flagship-versions.voicemod.net/1.2.1/VoicemodInstaller_1.2.1.exe)

* en

VOICEMOD PRIVACY POLICY
=======================

Updated: 17/05/2024

**Welcome to Voicemod**
-----------------------

If you’re reading this, first thing’s first: **Welcome to Voicemod!** We’re happy to have you here and want to make sure you fully understand our privacy policy and what it means for your information. 

Allow us to give a quick introduction. Voicemod is the proud owner of the domain name voicemod.net and all the websites hosted there. This privacy policy is a part of our General Terms of Use (TOU), and applies to how we handle your personal data whenever you use our websites, products, services, and applications (AKA any Voicemod Products).

If there’s one thing we want you to take away from this, it’s that we care about your privacy and are committed to protecting your information. This policy explains how we collect and process your data, making sure we comply with all the relevant regulations, like the European General Regulation on Data Protection (GDPR).

The access, use and maintenance of Voicemod Products involves the processing of personal information of its users according to the purposes informed in this policy.

By accessing and using Voicemod’s Products, you’re agreeing to the terms and conditions laid out in our policy. For any information  you provide or we collect from you, by using our Voicemod Products you accept that we’ll use it for the purposes we’re about to outline below and that you’ll follow our conditions and policies.

It’s important that you read this policy carefully to fully understand how we handle your data. We also encourage you to check back regularly for any updates or changes we may make.

If you don’t agree with our policies, no hard feelings! You can simply leave the website and choose not to use any of our services, applications, or products.

Now, let’s get into the nitty-gritty details. Voicemod Inc., Sucursal en España, with its registered office at Obispo Don Jerónimo 10, St. 46003, Valencia (Spain), being duly registered at Registro Mercantil de Valencia, Tomo 11462, Libro 8740, Folio 156, Hoja V-214069, Registration no. 1 is the controller to the processings of personal data below mentioned. If you have any questions please reach out to us using this [Contact Form](https://www.voicemod.net/support/?letstalk=Legal%20Terms+%26+Privacy).

**Voicemod Products**
---------------------

And finally, here’s a quick rundown of the awesome Voicemod products we often refer to:

* Voicemod web
* Voicemod desktop apps
* Mobile Controller app
* Community Content Hub -Community voices and Community sounds- (previously known as Tuna)
* Voicemod Go
* Voicemod Bot in Discord (previously known as Tuna Bot)
* VMGram
* Meme Generator

_All the information about our products is available in_ [_www.voicemod.net_](https://www.voicemod.net/) _and in VM Terms of Use (ToU)._

**Information that Voicemod Processes**
---------------------------------------

Here you can find all the information that Voicemod processes when using our products and services, but first let us tell you that we do not listen to your conversations when you are using the real-time voice changer features in VM Products and we do not listen to any voice recordings you provide for the purposes of AI voice creation.

### **Regarding All VM Products**

**Legal basis:** Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is party 

**Purposes:** 

1\. Managing user accounts and licences 

2\. Feedback and support  ([Support channel](https://www.voicemod.net/support/))

**Data processed:** 

1\. Personal information

2\. Contact information

3\. Voicemod user information

4\. Other social media accounts information (for social log-in or sign-up)

**Legal basis:** Our legitimate interest 

**Purposes:** 

1\. Services and apps functionality and their updates:

(a) To ensure that you can fully enjoy the services offered by Voicemod 

(b) To protect and maintain them and the websites’ environment. 

(c) Sometimes the processed info is used to analyse how much success Voicemod website has, how many users interact on it, etc. to develop and include better or new features as well as to get statistics for internal Voicemod study and knowledge

2\. Product personalization: your information helps us to provide, customise and improve the services/ products

3\. Sending information about updates, new functionalities, etc. regarding Voicemod products and services

4\. Information about the activities you perform in Voicemod using Desktop or/and Mobile Controller

5\. Information about the activities you perform and content you share on third-party sites (_e.g. Instagram, TikTok, Snapchat, Twitch, Twitter, Facebook_)

**Data processed:**

1\. Diagnostic related metadata – including error and performance data 

2\. Use and purchase history data and information.

3\. Contact information

4\. Behavioural information regarding your use of our products, etc.

5\. Username in the games or platforms where you use Voicemod. For further information you can read their Privacy Policies.

**Legal basis:** Legal obligation Specifically, the _Directive (EU) 2019/790 of The European Parliament and of the Council of 17 April 2019 on copyright and related rights in the Digital Single Market_

**Purpose:** Managing copyright infringement notices

**Data processed:** Your and the alleged infringer’s name, address, telephone number, e-mail and the potential infringing content and user For more information about this topic you can read VM **Community Guidelines** and **Copyright Policy.** 

### **Websites**

**Legal basis:**  Our legitimate interest 

**Purposes:** 

1\. Websites functionality

**Data processed:**

1\. Browsing data. For more information read our Cookies Policy.

### **Community Content Hub (previously known as Tuna)**

**Legal basis:** Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is party

**Purpose:**

1\. Provide you with the Community Content Hub related services.

**Data processed:** 

1\. Metadata related to the items uploaded by you to the Hub, regardless of the means by which you made available such items or content.

2\. Metadata related to your downloads of the Content hosted at the Hub. 

### **Voicemod Desktop apps** 

**Legal basis:** Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is party

**Purpose:** provide you with the Voicemod Desktop service

**Data processed:** behavioural information about your use of the service.

### **Voicemod Controller app for mobile**

**Legal basis:** Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is party.

**Purpose**: provide you with the services in the Controller app (i.e. to control Voicemod Desktop from your mobile device).

**Data**: 

1\. identification data (account id. information);

2\. metadata with regards to the mobile device from which you operate the app;

3\. metadata with regards to the computer from which you operate desktop;

### **Voicemod Go**

**Legal basis:** Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is party

**Purpose:** Provide you with the Products and App’s services

**Data processed:** 

1\. Audio, video (recordings), voice files (recordings) that you process with Voicemod Go when using it. 

2\. Content uploaded to the app in order to enjoy the services within the app.

3\. Final and derivative content produced with the app.

4\. Metadata regarding the Content, its upload and download.

**Note:** _Please keep in mind that we do not access neither to your camera or microphone for any other purpose than letting you directly record your videos and voice files directly with the app, which in any case will be processed locally for you to be able to apply our voice filters and avatars._

### **Voicemod Bot in Discord (previously known as Tuna Bot)**

**Legal basis:** Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is party

**Purpose:** Provide you with the services

**Data processed:**

1\. User information in Discord

2\. Metadata regarding where you use the Bot and what Voicemod Content you use.

### **VMGram**

VMGram is a client app of Telegram developed by Voicemod that allows Telegram users to enjoy Voicemod functionalities of voice modification and Sound Clips in their Telegram calls and chats. The communication service (calls, messages…) is provided by Telegram and to be able to use it through the VMGram interface you need to have a Telegram account.  
In this privacy policy we explain you the data collected and processed by the VMGram app, but for full information on privacy of the Telegram service, please refer to the Telegram privacy policy available at [Telegram Privacy Policy](https://telegram.org/privacy/eu), in particular for the data that is processed by Telegram independently from the permissions that you allow in this app, such as, for example, the public nature of your profile name, profile picture and “about” information) that Telegram collects when you create your account.

**Legal basis:** Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is party.

**Purpose:** Provide you with our services to be enjoyed in a Telegram-like app

**Data processed**:

1\. Metadata regarding the communication and texting, as well as related to the use of our services.

2\. Telephone no.

3\. Voice and audio recordings made with the app

And if you grant permission in the app, the app accesses, collects and processes the following:

4\. Your device’s camera and/or microphone to apply our audio processing to your voice and video calls or messages. All audio processing is performed locally on your device. We do not listen to your conversations or voice messages.

5\. Your device´s camera to allow you to take photos or videos directly within the app.

6\. Your contact list and images, so that the app can show who of your contacts are using VMGram (or Telegram) to connect with them and also let you share your images. Your name and profile image may be shown to other users depending on your settings, which you can control in the Privacy and Security section in the app. You can also write new contact information to your address book.

7\. Your device´s call log so that the Telegram service can verify your account.  

8\. Your location solely to enable you to share it with your contacts in your Telegram messages.  

9\. Your clipboard, to be able to paste text into a message, allowing the app to read data from your clipboard to do so.

10\. Your phone Bluetooth, which will allow the app to connect to other Bluetooth-connected devices, so that you can share files directly via Bluetooth

11\. Your personal profile data, if you want to set up or sync your user profile within the app.

12\. Your external (connectable) storage, to read and write in it directly from the app if you want to share or access the files you have in there.

13\. If you want to record audio messages, the app will ask as well for your permission to record the messages or calls within the app.

**Do not sell my data**
-----------------------

We would like you to know that we do not sell any of your information or data to third parties; all information and personal data is processed for the purpose of providing you our Voicemod Products and analyse them so that we can offer you the best possible.

**How we disclose your information** 
-------------------------------------

Sometimes we have to team up with other folks to get stuff done. So we might share some information with providers or vendors we bring on board, specifically, payment platforms like Xsolla and Paddle to process any payment regarding our Products. We also have cloud service providers like Google and AWS, which host our data and keep things running smoothly, and some handy tools and software to analyse how our users interact with Voicemod.

We may also share information about you that has been made anonymous, so that it cannot be easily used to identify you. We might use this anonymized information to give our partners or the public an idea of how awesome Voicemod is with some cool user stats.

**Data retention** 
-------------------

We hang on to your personal information for as long as we need it for the purposes we processed it. But there are certain rules and laws that come into play, which we are always mindful of. We might hold onto some data even if we don’t really need it anymore. Why? To make sure we’re covered when it comes to legal obligations, like taxes and other important business matters. We might even have to keep it if the law or the Security Forces or Courts ask us to. But fear not! Once we’re free to let it go, we’ll make sure to delete it for good.

Oh, and just so you know, any data we block and hang onto won’t be used by Voicemod. It’s all anonymized and locked away, far from our reach.

**International data transfers** 
---------------------------------

Voicemond runs the show from sunny Spain, but we also work with platforms and vendors from all around the world to bring you the best products. 

We mainly work with American vendors with servers all around the globe and mostly in Europe, which privacy rules are applicable to us due to our seat in Spain. However it’s also possible that personal data processing is carried out in other countries where our suppliers operate, including the United Kingdom, for example. In these instances, the processors involved are responsible for ensuring that your data is protected.

For EEA residents, please note that our international transfers outside the EEA either rely on the European Commission Standard Contractual Clauses which we sign with every vendor or the European Commission’s Adequacy Decisions on specific countries. In short, we make sure everything meets the GDPR’s standards, so your data is always in good hands.

In any case the data transfers that may be carried out will be those necessary to operate and supply the applications, products and services described for the indicated purposes. By using our applications, products and services, you acknowledge and agree that your data will be processed outside your country of residence.

**How we protect your information**
-----------------------------------

We take your privacy very seriously. We are committed to keeping your personal data safe and have all the necessary security measures in place, like top-notch admin, technical, and physical safeguards. We stay up to date with the latest technology to make sure your data doesn’t get messed with, lost, or accessed without permission.

That being said, although we do everything we can to protect your information, no security system is 100% foolproof. So, in the unlikely event that there is a breach or unauthorised access, Voicemod will not be liable. But rest assured, anyone working with Voicemod who needs access to your data is required to follow strict regulations to keep it safe. We don’t mess around with our users and their rights.

Keep in mind, sometimes our website or products may have links to third-party sites. These sites have their own policies in place, so it’s always a good idea to check out their terms, privacy policies, and cookie information before using their services. We do our best to pick trustworthy partners, but we can’t control how they handle your information.

**Minors**
----------

Voicemod can only be used if you are at least 16 years old. If you are 16 years old or older but not of legal age, please ask your parents or legal guardian to read this policy with you as they also accept this together with the Terms of Use. They are responsible for your use of Voicemod Products. We´ve drafted this policy as clearly as possible so that it can be easily understood by anyone, but If you have any question or consider that any clause or term is not sufficiently clear to you, contact us or/and your legal guardian to get clarification. 

**How to control your privacy** 
--------------------------------

Below is a list of rights that you may exercise to control your privacy. They come from the EU General Regulation on Data Protection (GDPR) and, because we are a people first company, we want to apply it to you even if you are not in the EU, since they are the most protective and comprehensive rights we know of. 

Being that said, here’s information about your rights as per the GDPR and how you can exercise them: 

* **Access your data**. You have the right to access and check your data, which you can easily do in the “my account-profile” section.
* **Correct your data**. We want to make sure your information is accurate and up to date, which is why you’re free to correct or request a change to any of your data.
* **Delete your data**. If you no longer want us to hold your data, you have the right to request its deletion.
* **Limit data processing**. You can ask us to limit the processing of your data if you believe it’s being handled inappropriately.
* **Object to data processing**. If we’re processing your data based on our legitimate interests, you have the right to object to it.
* **Withdraw consent**. If you previously gave us consent to process your data, you can withdraw that consent at any time.
* **Data portability**. If we’re processing your data based on your consent or the execution of a contract, you can request a copy of your data in a portable format.
* **No automated decisions**. You have the right to not be subjected to automated decision-making that could significantly affect you.
* **To file a complaint before the relevant supervisory authority.** If you’d have grounds to believe that any of your rights have not been properly fulfilled you can file a complaint before the relevant supervisory authority in your country.

These rights are important, and we’re here to ensure that you can exercise them easily. To do so or if you have questions, please reach out to us using this [Contact Form](https://www.voicemod.net/support/?letstalk=Legal%20Terms+%26+Privacy).

**Reach out to us!** 
---------------------

Need to get in touch? Just contact us through our privacy [Contact Form](https://www.voicemod.net/support/?letstalk=Legal%20Terms+%26+Privacy) and let us know what’s on your mind. We’ll jump right on it and process your request faster than you can say “privacy protection”! We’re all about keeping things GDPR-compliant and following the laws and procedures in place to keep your data safe. 

As our offices are located in Spain, should you like to lodge a complaint, you can do so either before your relevant supervisory authority or the [Spanish Data Protection Agency](https://www.aepd.es/es) (AEPD), which you can reach out at 6, Jorge Juan – 28001 Madrid (Spain) or by calling (+34) 912 663 517. There’s also a [specific channel](https://sedeagpd.gob.es/sede-electronica-web/) you can contact them at for any data privacy needs.

**Special information about Recruiting – Corporate website**
------------------------------------------------------------

Voicemod processes the below data when recruiting candidates. All the information explained above about how we handle and process your data, what your rights are and how to contact us also apply for this processing. 

**Legal basis:**  Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is party or in order to take steps at the request of the data subject prior to entering into a contract 

**Purposes:** 

1\. Hiring (Recruiting process, interviews and all phases from the application to the confirmation of the job placement)

**Data processed:** 

1\. Contact information;

2\. Personal information;

3\. Professional information;

4\. Academic experiences and information;

5\. Occupational information.

6\. Other information included in CVs or applications

**Legal basis:**  Our legitimate interest 

**Purposes:** 

1\. Recruiting: Voicemod uses third-party platforms for publishing job offers and receiving your CVs such as Lever or LinkedIn or third-party entities (_e.g. universities)_ You can read more about Lever’s privacy through the following [link](https://www.lever.co/privacy/). Also the privacy policy of LinkedIN can be found [here](https://es.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy?).

**Data processed:**

1\. CVs, photos, telephone, address, professional experience, ID and any other information that the potential candidate had included in such platforms.

**Special information about Voicemod improvement projects**
-----------------------------------------------------------

Voicemod may run from time to time concrete projects to improve its services. This processing only takes place if you actively opt-in, and this data is anonymised as soon as it’s collected. All the information explained above about how we handle and process your data, what your rights are and how to contact us also apply for this processing. 

**Legal basis:** Consent by the data subject (you) to the processing of his or her (your) personal data for the purposes hereinafter mentioned

**Purposes**:

1\. Improvement of our services (training our technologies to serve you the best Products)

**Data processed**:

1\. Voice samples of your voice

Let's Connect

[Our Story](https://www.voicemod.com/our-story) · [Newsroom](https://www.voicemod.com/newsroom) · [Careers](https://www.voicemod.com/careers) · [Blog](https://www.voicemod.net/blog/) · [Support](https://www.voicemod.net/support/) · [Developer Kit](https://www.voicemod.net/developers/)

© 2024 Voicemod Inc., Sucursal en España·[Privacy Policy](https://www.voicemod.net/privacy/ "Privacy Policy")·[Terms](https://www.voicemod.net/terms-of-use/)·[Cookies Policy](https://www.voicemod.net/cookies-policy/ "Cookies Policy")·[3rd Party Software Report](https://voicemod.notion.site/3rd-Party-Software-Report-for-Voicemod-Apps-3ce7ec8daebb4d228b2bf2310daeccd5)·[Legal](https://www.voicemod.net/legal/)·

English
